anime-w.com 2017-12-03

# Welcome to Ern Online

|  | 

  Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting a Lrnforex Web site. This policy explains how we use personal information collected on Web sites owned by Lrnforex. Please read this privacy policy before using any Lrnforex Web site. By using a Lrnforex Web site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. 

This policy may be changed at any time. Any changes will be posted. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy each and every time you visit a Lrnforex Web site. 

**Cookies**  
Lrnforex Web sites use cookies to collect information about users. Some of these cookies are from third-party advertisers and advertising networks. Most browsers give users the option to turn off cookies. To turn off cookies on your browser, please see its documentation or help options. 

**Information Collection**  
We collect certain information about users who visit this site, including user actions and click paths, domain name/IP addresses and browser types, as well as other information. We use this information mainly to track referrals, advertisements and user behavior. 

**Distribution of Information**  
We may share information with government agencies or other companies helping us to investigate or prevent fraud. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required to do so by law; or, (2) preventing or attempting to prevent actual or potential unauthorized actions or fraud; or, (3) investigating past fraud. We also share information with third-party advertisers and advertising networks. Privacy Policies of Web Sites Hyperlinked to from Lrnforex Web sites We are not responsible for the policies of Web sites that we hyperlink to. If you visit other Web sites hyperlinked to from a Lrnforex Web site, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites. 

**Privacy Contact Information**  
If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about my privacy policy, please email us at info at our Lrnforex.com   
  
---|---|---
